var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أَبَدًا",
        "answer": "forever",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "abadan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٌ",
        "answer": "anyone",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "aḥadun",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدًا",
        "answer": "(to) anyone",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "aḥadan",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "He has taken",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "But",
        "pcklId": "646",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "647",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2800",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2801",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2802",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2803",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(are) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2804",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2805",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2806",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2807",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2808",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2809",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "711",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "712",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or (whether)",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَدًا",
        "answer": "a (distant) term",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "amadan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآمَنَّا",
        "answer": "so we believe",
        "pcklId": "541",
        "tlit": "faāmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we believed",
        "pcklId": "542",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنْ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "543",
        "tlit": "yu'min",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسُ",
        "answer": "the men",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-insu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَخْسًا",
        "answer": "any loss",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bakhsan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثَ",
        "answer": "will raise",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yabʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْلَغُوا",
        "answer": "they have conveyed",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ablaghū",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَاغًا",
        "answer": "(the) notification",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "balāghan",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَدُّ",
        "answer": "(the) Majesty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jaddu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "will appoint",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "yajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِنُّ",
        "answer": "and the jinn",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wal-jinu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجِيرَنِي",
        "answer": "can protect me",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yujīranī",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَسًا",
        "answer": "guards",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥarasan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحَرَّوْا",
        "answer": "have sought",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥarraw",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْصَىٰ",
        "answer": "and He takes account",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥṣā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَطَبًا",
        "answer": "firewood",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥaṭaban",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحَاطَ",
        "answer": "and He has encompassed",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥāṭa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(they will) abide",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفِهِ",
        "answer": "behind him",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "khalfihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُ",
        "answer": "he will fear",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yakhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَدْرِي",
        "answer": "we know",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nadrī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرِي",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "adrī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوا",
        "answer": "call",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "tadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُوهُ",
        "answer": "calling (upon) Him",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "yadʿūhu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْعُو",
        "answer": "I call upon",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "adʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) other than",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "dūna",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "the Remembrance",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَأَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "ra-aw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "with our Lord",
        "pcklId": "904",
        "tlit": "birabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord ",
        "pcklId": "905",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "906",
        "tlit": "rabbuhum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "in his Lord",
        "pcklId": "907",
        "tlit": "birabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "908",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "909",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "910",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "911",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالٌ",
        "answer": "men",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "rijālun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرِجَالٍ",
        "answer": "in (the) men",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "birijālin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِسَالَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messages",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "warisālātihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Messages",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "risālāti",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "warasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّشْدِ",
        "answer": "the right way",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-rush'di",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَشَدًا",
        "answer": "a right path",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "rashadan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَشَدًا",
        "answer": "(the) right path",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "rashadan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَشَدًا",
        "answer": "right path",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "rashadan",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَصَدًا",
        "answer": "a guard",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "raṣadan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَصَدًا",
        "answer": "waiting",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "raṣadan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْتَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He has approved",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ir'taḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَهَقًا",
        "answer": "(in) burden",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "rahaqan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَهَقًا",
        "answer": "any burden",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "rahaqan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرِيدَ",
        "answer": "is intended",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "urīda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "intends",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَزَادُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "so they increased them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "fazādūhum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسَاجِدَ",
        "answer": "the masjids",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-masājida",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفِيهُنَا",
        "answer": "the foolish among us",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "safīhunā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَسْقَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "surely We (would) have given them to drink",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "la-asqaynāhum",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْلُكْهُ",
        "answer": "He will make him enter",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yasluk'hu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْلُكُ",
        "answer": "makes to march",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yasluku",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَمَ",
        "answer": "submits",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "aslama",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) Muslims",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "heard",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "we heard",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَمَعَ",
        "answer": "listened",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "is'tamaʿa",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَمِعِ",
        "answer": "listens",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yastamiʿi",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلسَّمْعِ",
        "answer": "for hearing",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "lilssamʿi",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "shadīdan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَرٌّ",
        "answer": "whether evil",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "asharrun",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُشْرِكَ",
        "answer": "we will associate",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "nush'rika",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُشْرِكُ",
        "answer": "I associate",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ush'riku",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَطَطًا",
        "answer": "an excessive transgression",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shaṭaṭan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِهَابًا",
        "answer": "a flaming fire",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "shihāban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشُهُبًا",
        "answer": "and flaming fires",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "washuhuban",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "513",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاحِبَةً",
        "answer": "a wife",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "ṣāḥibatan",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَعَدًا",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṣaʿadan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥūna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضْعَفُ",
        "answer": "(is) weaker",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aḍʿafu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَرَائِقَ",
        "answer": "(are on) ways",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṭarāiqa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّرِيقَةِ",
        "answer": "the Way",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ṭarīqati",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنَّا",
        "answer": "thought",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ẓanannā",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "thought",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you thought",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ẓanantum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنَّا",
        "answer": "[we] have become certain",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ẓanannā",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظْهِرُ",
        "answer": "He reveals",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yuẓ'hiru",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدُ",
        "answer": "(the) slave",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "ʿabdu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجَبًا",
        "answer": "amazing",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ʿajaban",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعْجِزَ",
        "answer": "we will cause failure",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nuʿ'jiza",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعْجِزَهُ",
        "answer": "we can escape Him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nuʿ'jizahu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدَدًا",
        "answer": "(in) number",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ʿadadan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدَدًا",
        "answer": "(in) number",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ʿadadan",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "turns away",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'riḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْصِ",
        "answer": "disobeys",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yaʿṣi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَيَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "then they will know",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "fasayaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "That He may make evident",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "liyaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمُ",
        "answer": "(The) All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "841",
        "tlit": "ʿālimu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "Exalted is",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "taʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعُوذُونَ",
        "answer": "who sought refuge",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaʿūdhūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَدَقًا",
        "answer": "(in) abundance",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghadaqan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْبِهِ",
        "answer": "His unseen",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ghaybihi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْتِنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "That We might test them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "linaftinahum",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِدَدًا",
        "answer": "different",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "qidadan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "a Quran",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "whether is near",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "aqarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاسِطُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) unjust",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-qāsiṭūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاسِطُونَ",
        "answer": "the unjust",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-qāsiṭūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْعُدُ",
        "answer": "sit",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "naqʿudu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَاعِدَ",
        "answer": "positions",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "maqāʿida",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَلُّ",
        "answer": "and fewer",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-aqallu",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1584",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "1585",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "speak ",
        "pcklId": "1586",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1587",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1588",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1589",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1590",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1591",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَامَ",
        "answer": "stood up",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "qāma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "they had remained",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "is'taqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "any lie",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "(of) all",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادُوا",
        "answer": "they almost",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "kādū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "1311",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) were",
        "pcklId": "1312",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "1313",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "We",
        "pcklId": "1314",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "they will be",
        "pcklId": "1315",
        "tlit": "fakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُونَ",
        "answer": "became",
        "pcklId": "1316",
        "tlit": "yakūnūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَدًا",
        "answer": "a compacted mass",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "libadan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْتَحَدًا",
        "answer": "any refuge",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mul'taḥadan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَسْنَا",
        "answer": "sought to touch",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lamasnā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلِئَتْ",
        "answer": "filled (with)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "muli-at",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "possess",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "amliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِرًا",
        "answer": "(in) helpers",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "nāṣiran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَرٌ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nafarun",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارَ",
        "answer": "(is the) Fire",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "It guides",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the Guidance",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَرَبًا",
        "answer": "(by) flight",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "haraban",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَجَدْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "but we found it",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "fawajadnāhā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدْ",
        "answer": "will find",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "yajid",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِدَ",
        "answer": "can I find",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ajida",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "It has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "they are promised",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "yūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "you are promised",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْهِ",
        "answer": "him",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "yadayhi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "72",
        "ayah": "27"
    }
]; 
export default words;